Dave Chapman Papers
Dave Chapman Papers
- Subject files (1968 accession)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1960 (Box II / 26)
    - WGBH-TV - New England Station, 1959 (Box II / 26)
  - Employee Kit, 1965 (Box II / 27)
  - Fox River Forge, 1956 (Box II / 27)
  - General Electric Company, 1953-1956 (Box II / 27)
  - Haire Publications, 1958-1959 (Box II / 27)
  - Hankscraft Company, 1954-1962 (Box II / 27)
  - Home Appliance Builder, 1947-1962 (Box II / 27)
  - International Cooperation Administration
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box II / 28)
    - Bank Correspondence, 1956 (Box II / 28)
    - Central America and Caribbean Area, 1956 (Box II / 28)
    - Costa Rica, Correspondence re, 1956 (Box II / 28)
    - Jamaica, Correspondence re, 1956-1957 (Box II / 28)
    - Liberia, Correspondence re, 1956 (Box II / 28)
    - Mexico, Correspondence re, 1956 (Box II / 28)
    - Pakistan, Correspondence re, 1955 (Box II / 28)
    - Pakistan, Correspondence re, 1956 (Box II / 29)
    - Pakistan Institute of Industrial Design, 1957 (Box II / 29)
    - Pakistan - Maps of, Correspondence re, 1948-1950 (Box II / 29)
    - El Salvador, Correspondence re, 1956 (Box II / 29)
    - Salvador Tour, Correspondence re, 1956 (Box II / 29)
    - Surinam, Correspondence re, 1956 (Box II / 29)
    - Customs (Box II / 29)
    - Forms (Box II / 29)
    - Newspaper and Magazine Articles (Box II / 29)
    - Photography, 1952 (Box II / 30)
    - Proposals, 1955 (Box II / 30)
    - Reference Material, 1955-1956 (Box II / 30)
    - Reference Material and Product Write-Ups, 1950-1960 (Box II / 30)
    - Reports, 1956; 2 folders (Box II / 30)
    - Reports - Daily and Progress, 1955-1956 (Box II / 30)
    - Reports - Final, 1955-1956 (Box II / 30)
    - Reports - Interim Reports, 1956 (Box II / 30)
    - Reports - Interim Reports, 1965 (Box II / 30)
  - Institutions, 1953-1960 (Box II / 31)
  - Jefferson Electric, 1954-1963 (Box II / 31)
  - Journal of the Royal Society of Arts, 1960-1961 (Box II / 31)
  - Luce, 1959-1965 (Box II / 32)
  - Montgomery Ward and Company, 1955-1960 (Box II / 32)
  - Product Engineering, 1954-1961 (Box II / 32)
  - Public Relations
    - Advertizing Age (reprints), 1951 (Box II / 33)
    - Art Director and Studio News, 1952 (Box II / 33)
    - Art and Industry - Four Spokes to the Wheel, 1951 (Box II / 33)
    - Art and Industry - Story on Parker, 1951 (Box II / 33)
    - Business Week, 1950 (Box II / 33)
    - Chicago Daily News "ROTO" (Box II / 33)
    - Chicago Daily News, 1951; 3 folders (Box II / 33)
    - Chicago Daily News, 1951 (Box II / 34)
    - Chicago Tribune, 1951 (Box II / 34)
    - Chicago Sunday Tribune, 1951; 2 folders (Box II / 34)
    - D.T.I. News, 1951 (Box II / 34)
    - Designer's Mailer, 1952 (Box II / 34)
    - Designs, Notes, 1951 (Box II / 34)
    - Durez, Plastics and Chemicals, Inc. - Brochures, undated (Box II / 34)
    - Electrical Manufacturing, 1949 (Box II / 34)
    - Fortune, 1952 (Box II / 34)
    - Fortune - Research Material, 1953-1956 (Box II / 34)
    - Katzman, Field & Ware - Black Diamond Mink Label, 1953 (Box II / 35)
    - Living With Flowers, 1952 (Box II / 35)
    - Printing for Commerce, 1952 (Box II / 35)
    - Publicity Clippings, 1948-1952 (Box II / 35)
    - Publicity Requests, 1944-1949 (Box II / 35)
    - Published Stories, 1953 (Box II / 35)
    - Technometer, 1951 (Box II / 35)
    - Tide, 1947 (Box II / 35)
    - Wall Street Journal, 1951 (Box II / 35)
  - Public Relations News, 1954-1960 (Box II / 36)
  - Small Homes Guide, Inc. - Home Modernizing, 1955-1956 (Box II / 36)
  - Speeches Given, Correspondence re, 1964 (Box II / 36)
  - Tear Sheets- Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box II / 36)
  - Tear Sheets - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box II / 37)
  - Yacht Search, 1959-1962 (Box II / 37)
  - Oversize material (Box II / 38)
- Color slides (1968 accession)
  - 1966 (Box III / 1)
- General files
  - Photos
    - Farm Equipment American Havester, 1950's (Box 1)
  - CGY
    - CGY Communications Program, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Executives Responses to CGY Proposed Letterheads, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Dave Chapman Inc.
    - Dave Chapman Inc. Industrial Design (Oversize 1, 2)
    - Dave Chapman Inc. Industrial Design, and Engineering (Box 1)
    - Dave Chapman, Goldsmith, and Yamasaki, Inc. Design, Planning, and Programing (Box 1)
    - Dave Chapman, Goldsmith, and Yamasaki, Inc. A Sales Building Public Relations Program (Box 1)
  - Magazines
    - Design Steel 69, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Design USA, June 1965 (Box 1)
    - Metal Products Manufacturing, August 1967 (Box 1)
    - Modern Supplementary Classroom Design (Box 1)
    - Nations Schools, February 1967 (Box 1)
    - Practical Builder, June 1966 (Box 1)
    - Prognosis, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Reprints of photos and articles (Box 1)
    - Reprints (Oversize 3)
  - ASSA
    - Suggested Design Directions for the American Association of School Adminstrators Annual Convention, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Allied Farm Equipment
    - Corporate Identification and Procedures, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Allied Radio and Knight Electronics
    - Proposal for Design Program, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Allis Chalmers
    - Design Development Progam: Feasibility Study, 1968 (Box 2)
  - American Hospital Supply
    - Identification and Packaging Program (Box 2)
  - American Iron and Steel Institute
    - Slides (Box 2)
    - Presentation: Second Stage Development/The American Iron and Steel Institute Exhibit, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Bauer and Black
    - Proposal and Cost/Time Estimates on Packaging Program for Elastic Goods Lines of Bauer and Black, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Brunswick
    - Photos (Box 2)
    - Wood School Furniture (Box 2)
    - Brunswick Color Keyed System, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Brunswick-Balke-Collender Company Identification plan, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Catalog-Furniture & Equipment for the library Resource Center, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Carr, Adams, and Collier
    - Research and Design Program for Carr, Adams, and Collier, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Chance Vought Aircraft Co.
    - Proposal and Cost/Time Estimate Phase I: Evaluation of the Market for Recreational Boats, 1958 (Box 2)
  - City National Bank & Trust
    - Identification Progam (Box 2)
  - Corning Glass
    - Preliminary Design Analysis (Box 2A)
  - Crane
    - A Proposal, 1939 (Box 2A)
  - Creative Packing
    - Concept Sketches, plastic packaging, 1963 (Box 2A)
  - DuKane Corporation
    - Proposals for three projects, together with working procedures, 1971 (Box 2A)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratorv
    - Design Research Program for Educational Facilities Laboratories, schedules, correspondence, clippings, 1959-1960 (Box 2A)
    - Middle School: a Report an a Conference to Plan a Middle School - Bedford Public Schools and Educational Facilities Laboratories
    - Design For TV (Box 2A)
    - Modern Supplementary Classroom Design, prepared by Panelfab Products (Box 2A)
    - A School for the 70's: The Module of One (Box 2A)
    - Implementing The Module of One Audio-Visual Cassette Systems (Box 2A)
  - Elizabeth Arden
    - Proposal: To Elizabeth Arden Sales Corp. for Remodeling, 1971 (Box 2A)
  - Eljer
    - Health and Beauty Rooms: Plans, 1960; 1961 (Box 2A)
    - Identification Program (Box 2A)
  - Fel-Pro
    - Fel-Pro Materials and Engineering Guide (Box 3)
  - Ford
    - General information sent to Ford, 1967 (Box 3)
  - General Sarnoff Research Labs
    - A Brief: The Amateur Instrumental Music Industry, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Great Western United Corporation
    - Proposal for Comprehensive Industrial Design Program, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Hamilton Beach
    - Concept sketches, electric knife variations, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Hirsh
    - Corporate Identification Manual (Box 3)
  - Hussman
    - Supermarket survey, 1956-1964 (Box 3)
    - Product line work, thru 1964 (Box 3)
  - ICA (International Cooperation Adminstration)
    - Costa Rica: Industrial Design Survey Report (Box 3)
    - Surinam: Industrial Design Survey Report (Box 3)
    - El Salvador: A Program of Design for the Small Industries and Crafts Program Of El Salvador (Box 3)
    - Iran: Design Team Activity Report, Oct. 1957 thru July 1958 (Box 3)
    - Iran: Catalog of Furniture Produced Under thr Furniture Design Project, Iran and Lebanon, Feb.1959 - Dec. 1959 (Box 3)
    - Iran: Product catalog, in Arabic (Box 3)
    - Iran: Final Report, 1959 (Box 3)
  - International Havester
    - Seating Criteria for Farming Equipment, 1956 (Box 4)
    - 195X Refrigeration, Proposal for modular kitchen appliances (Box 4)
  - Interstate United
    - Corporate Identification Manual (Box 4)
  - Johnson Motors
    - Outboard motor sketches, 1958 (Box 4)
    - Photos of outboard development (Box 4)
    - Johnson Motors Identification Program (Box 4)
    - Company Identification Design Program (Box 4)
    - Sales literature, 1970 (Box 4)
    - Proposed Johnson Boat Line, Summary, July 1961 (Box 4)
  - Lear Siegler, Inc./Beauti-Glide Co.
    - The Management of Products in the Decade Ahead (Box 4)
  - Maytag
    - Identification Program Proposal (Box 4)
    - Corporate Identification Manual (Box 4)
  - Memorex
    - Program Proposal For Memorex Corporation, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Molson
    - Identification Program, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Montogomery Ward
    - Product Engineering Program, Conference notes, 1959-1960 (Box 4A)
    - Identification Plan (Conference Copy), 1956 (Box 4A)
    - Identification Data and Specification Manual for Garden Mark line (Box 4A)
  - NASA
    - Design Proposal, 1965 (Box 4A)
  - Nekoosa-Edwards
    - Proposal for a Design Program of Company and Brand Identity, 1959 (Box 4A)
  - Northwest Orient
    - Advertising counsel from Design Research Inc. (Box 4A)
  - Parker Pen
    - Packaging Program (Box 4A)
  - Peoples Gas Company
    - Supplementary Slides Showing CGY Projects Pertinent to Peoples Gas Company Exhibit (Box 4A)
  - Quality Chekd Dairy Products
    - Packaging Design Program Proposal and Cost-Time Estimate, 1958 (Box 4A)
  - RCA
    - Slides (Box 4A)
    - Sketches (Box 4A)
    - Instrumentation studies, 1966 (Box 4A)
    - 710 TV models, 1966 (Box 4A)
    - 700 line, radios, TV, 1965 (Box 4A)
    - 727 tape recorder, 1967 (Box 4A)
    - Bag and floater radios, 1968 (Box 4A)
    - Youth and Speciality Product line, 1967-1968 (Box 4A)
    - Packaging, 1968 (Box 4A)
    - Stereo cardboard models, 1967 (Box 4A)
    - Homefax presentation, 1968 (Box 4A)
    - Homefax Demonstration and Program Examples, 1968 (Box 4A)
    - Demographic Character of the Mid 70s: as they relate to RCA Product lines (Box 4A)
  - Sears
    - Design and Packaging Development, baby care products (Box 5)
    - Seiko (Box 5)
    - Clock sketches and surface samples, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Preliminary Line Study, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Simoniz
    - Packaging proposals, small copy (Box 5)
    - Oversize material (Oversize 4)
  - Southern Desk
    - Proposal for: The Design of a new Line of College Library Furniture, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Union Tank Car Co.
    - Proposal for Corporate Identity Program, 1968 (Box 5)
  - USAF Academy
    - Mission: Cadet Environment, small copy, 1955 (Box 5)
    - Oversize material (Oversize 5)
  - U.S. Information Agency
    - Education in U.S.A., exhibit proposal, 1968 (Box 5)
    - Document of Intent for Participation in Exhibit "Education Technology USA", 1968 (Box 5)
  - University Patents
    - Preliminary Design Studies of Adaptation of Metal Fiber Materials to Comsumer Products, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Thomas J. Webb Co.
    - Packaging Design Program: Proposal, Estimate and Timetable, 1957 (Box 5)
  - Westclox Division
    - Proposal for A Design Study of the Big Ben and Baby Ben Key-Wind Clocks, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Western Forestry Center
    - Proposal for Design of Exhibits for Forestry Industry Center, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Weyerhauser
    - Identification Program Proposal and Cost-Time Estimate, 1958 (Box 5)
  - Worthington
    - Gamon-Calmet gauges, design evaluation and concept sketches, 1967 (Box 5)
    - Mason-Neilan gauges, design program proposal, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Wood Marketing Inc
    - Wonderful World of Wood Program (Box 5)
    - Caravan Story (Box 5)
    - Product photos (Box 6)
    - Reprints (Box 6)
  - Slides
    - A.B. Dick (Box 6)
    - Acoustiflex (Box 6)
    - AID (Box 6)
    - ALCOA (Box 7)
    - Allied Farm Equiptment (Box 7)
    - Allis Chalmers (Box 7)
    - American Hospital Supply (Box 7)
    - American Iron and Steel Institute (Box 7)
    - Apex (Box 7)
    - Banker's Life (Box 7)
    - Barton Distilling (Box 7)
    - Baxter Lab (Box 7)
    - Beltone (Box 7)
    - Best-O-Wire (Box 7)
    - Bon Ami (Box 7)
    - Borg (Box 7)
    - Brunswick (Box 8)
    - Buddig (Box 8)
    - B.H. Bunn (Box 8)
    - BVI (Burgess) (Box 8)
    - Continental Assurance (Box 8)
    - Chiffon (Box 8)
    - Cooper (Box 8)
    - Corning Glass (Box 8)
    - Crippled Children and Adults (Box 8)
    - Educational Facilities Lab (Box 8)
    - Eljer (Box 8)
    - Fel-Pro (Box 9)
    - First Federal of Wisconsin (Box 9)
    - Fransiscan (Box 9)
    - Gabriel (Box 9)
    - General Electric (Box 9)
    - Gordon Street (Box 9)
    - Hallmark (Box 9)
    - Hamilton Beach (Box 9)
    - Hammond (Box 9)
    - HBJ (Box 9)
    - Herman Nelson (Box 9)
    - Hudson's Bay (Box 9)
    - IAI (Box 9)
    - Igloo (Box 9)
    - Illinois Testing Lab (Box 10)
    - Imperial Tobacco Co. (Box 10)
    - International Harvester (Box 10)
    - Jacobsen (Box 10)
    - Japan Air Lines (Box 10)
    - Jefferson (Box 10)
    - Johnson (Box 10)
    - Keebler (Box 10)
    - Kroehler (Box 10)
    - Leigh Electric (Box 10)
    - Libby (Box 10)
    - Eli Lilly (Box 10)
    - MacGregor (Box 10)
    - Maytag (Box 10)
    - Mead Johnson (Box 10)
    - Molson (Box 11)
    - Montgomery Ward (Box 11)
    - MS (Box 11)
    - My-Maid (Box 11)
    - NSC (Box 11)
    - Nekoosa Edwards (Box 11)
    - Nimrod (Box 11)
    - Ovaltine (Box 11)
    - Owens-Corning (Box 11)
    - Pabst (Box 11)
    - Parker (Box 11)
    - Plato's Place (Box 11)
    - PSC (Box 11)
    - Puritron (Box 11)
    - Raburn (Box 11)
    - RCA (Box 11)
    - Reliance Electric (Box 12)
    - Rexall (Box 12)
    - RHM (Box 12)
    - Rutgers University (Box 12)
    - Ryder (Box 12)
    - Schlitz (Box 12)
    - Seagram (Box 12)
    - Sears (Box 12)
    - Selk (Box 12)
    - Siegler (Box 12)
    - Simoniz (Box 12)
    - Southern Desk (Box 12)
    - Speed-O-Print (Box 12)
    - Stewart Warner (Box 13)
    - Sun-Times (Box 13)
    - Talk-A-Phone (Box 13)
    - Tavern Club (Box 13)
    - Tex-Made (Box 13)
    - TTI (Box 13)
    - University Patents (Box 13)
    - USL (Box 13)
    - USS Chemical GATX (Box 13)
    - Vermeer (Box 13)
    - Wescor (Box 13)
    - Weyerhauser (Box 13A)
    - Wood Marketing Institute (Box 13A)
    - Worthington (Box 13A)
    - John Wood Co. (Box 13A)
    - Unidentified (Box 13A)
    - General Presentation Slides, Slide Sheets Duplicate Slides, Boxed (Box 14)
    - Duplicate Slides, boxed (Box 14, 15)
- Advertising work
  - Industrial Designs
    - Hamilton Beach
      - Final artwork, Cookbook Blender #8, Jan 7 1966 (Package 1)
    - Interstate United
      - Drawings, 6 items (Package 1)
      - Drawings, 4 items + 1 folder (Package 1)
      - Truck drawings, 3 items (Package 1)
      - Combined drawings, 3 items (Package 1)
    - Laurentide Biere-Ale
      - Drawings and models, 21 items (Package 1)
    - Maytag and Company
      - Proposed signs, pencil drafts, sketches, 1965; 29 items (Package 2)
      - Alphabet charts, negative photocopies, 2 items (Package 2)
      - Sketches, 23 items (Package 2)
      - Blue ink sketches, 60 items (Package 2)
      - Identification program proposals, 25 items (Package 3)
      - Sketches of artists' ideas, 16 items (Package 4)
      - Corporate identification manual: final art for project, 17 items (Package 4)
      - Miscellaneous poster materials, 100 items (Package 5)
      - Artists' ideas, drawings, advertising symbols, miscellaneous shipping labels, brochures, interoffice correspondence, 325 items (Package 5)
  - Owens-Corning
    - Posters, layout, fiberglass insulation, foil wrap studies, 4 items (Package 6)
    - "Batt Blankets," building insulation, 2 models (Package 6)
    - Fiberglass models, 4 items (Package 6)
  - Simoniz
    - Wax containers and applicators, 42 items (Package 7)
    - Package lines sketches, 78 items (Package 8)
    - Final art: Reddi Clean, negative photocopy, 3 items (Package 8)
    - Final art: Reddi Foam, negative photocopy, 2 items (Package 8)
    - Final art: Reddi Foam, sketches, 1 item (Package 8)
    - Final art: Reddi Clean, sketches, 2 items (Package 8)
    - Vista One Step Cleaner Wax, 9 items (Package 8)
    - Vinylwax, sketches, 2 items (Package 8)
    - Lock and Key Floor Finish, sketches, 3 items (Package 8)
    - Lock and Key Floor Finish, sketches, 2 items (Package 8)
    - Simoniz service areas, negative photocopy, 18 items (Package 8)
    - Presentation charts, negative photocopy, 18 items (Package 8)
    - Simoniz products, photograph, 1 item (Package 8)
    - Current format evaluation charts, printed material, 3 items (Package 8)
    - Mounted sketches, 8 items (Package 8)
    - Designs of sketches, 21 items (Package 9)
    - Body Sheen Liquid Polish, advertising layouts, negative photocopy, 4 items (Package 9)
    - Vista Paste Wax, advertising layouts, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 9)
    - Toni, advertising layout, negative photocopy, 1 items (Package 9)
    - Simoniz Household Line Guide Chart, 2 items (Package 9)
    - Simoniz, miscellaneous poster material, 28 items (Package 9)
    - Simoniz products, 3 items (Package 9)
    - Correspondence, Nov 27 1961; 1 items (Package 9)
    - Reddi Starch Sprayer, negative photocopy, 2 items (Package 9)
    - Aerosol Spray Handles, sketches, 2 items (Package 9)
    - Aerosol Sprayer, color sketch, 1 item (Package 9)
    - Miracle Liquid, negative photocopy of both sides, 2 items (Package 9)
    - Negative copies front and back (Package 9)
    - Stik-Stik, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 9)
    - Auto Interior Cleaner, negative photocopy, 3 items (Package 9)
    - Windshield De Icer, negative photocopy, 3 items (Package 9)
    - Titan All Purpose Cleaner Wax, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 9)
    - Reddi Products, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 9)
    - One Shot Drain Cleaner, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 9)
    - Vista Miracle Liquid, negative photocopy, 5 items (Package 9)
    - Auto Metal Polish, negative photocopy, 3 items (Package 9)
    - Vinyl wax, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 9)
    - Lock and Key Floor Finish, negative photocopy, 10 items (Package 9)
    - Vista Miracle Mist, finished label products, 3 items (Package 9)
    - Adhesive Stick Dispensers, photograph, 1 item (Package 9)
    - Adhesive Stick Dispensers, photograph, 1 item (Package 9)
    - Unidentified container, August 21, 1962; 1 items (Package 9)
    - Confidential extrusion sketch, March 2, 1962; 2 items (Package 9)
    - Pencil holder, sketch, 5 items (Package 9)
    - Plastic bottle, 22 oz., negative photocopy, June 2, 1961; 2 items (Package 9)
    - Plastic bottle, 14 oz., sketches, June 8, 1961; 2 items (Package 9)
    - Plastic bottle, 14 oz., sketch, May 16, 1961; 1 item (Package 9)
    - Plastic bottle, sketch, June 9, 1961; 3 items (Package 9)
    - Plastic bottle, negative photocopy, June 9, 1961; 1 item (Package 9)
    - Plastic bottle, 28 oz., sketches, June 14, 1961; 3 items (Package 9)
    - Plastic bottle cap, 14 oz., 1 item (Package 9)
    - Plastic bottle, miscellaneous sketches, 5 items (Package 9)
    - Can, paper label for polish, negative photocopy, November 11, 1963; 1 item (Package 10)
    - One Step Wood Wax can, paper label, negative photocopy, December 2, 1963; 3 items (Package 10)
    - Tone can, paper label, negative photocopy, February 21, 1964; 1 item (Package 10)
    - VIV Floor Wax can, paper label, negative photocopy, January 26, 1961; 1 item (Package 10)
    - Vista can, paper label, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 10)
    - Miscellaneous poster material, 10 items (Package 10)
    - Miracle Liquid, bottle label, sketch, September 27, 1962; 1 item (Package 10)
    - Gift Stat Coupon Program poster, November 6, 1962; 1 item (Package 10)
    - Vista Floor Cleaner, label, negative photocopy, November 5, 1962; 2 items (Package 10)
    - Vista One Step Cleaner/Wax, negative photocopy, December 21, 1962; 3 items (Package 10)
    - Vista Round Can Wax, negative photocopy, November 4, 1960; 2 items (Package 10)
    - Sketches, 6 items (Package 10)
    - Simoniz Polish package, sketches, November 7, 1963; 5 items (Package 10)
    - Wax box, sketches, December 10, 1963; 3 items (Package 10)
    - Wax applicators, sketches, July 4, 1963; 6 items (Package 10)
    - Wax applicators, sketches, July 5, 1963; 5 items (Package 10)
    - Wax containers, sketches, July 8, 1963; 9 items (Package 10)
    - Wax products, sketches, October 14, 1963; 6 items (Package 10)
    - Wax products, sketches, 15 items (Package 10)
    - Miscellaneous poster material, 23 items (Package 10)
    - Labels, one sheet (Package 10)
    - Vista Floor Cleaner, negative photocopies, 2 items (Package 10)
    - VIC and Reddi Starch, labels, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 10)
    - Vista, paper label, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 10)
    - Instruction label proofs, negative photocopy, 3 items (Package 10)
    - Lock & Key Remover, negative photocopy, August 4, 1961 (Package 10)
    - Lock & Key Remover, negative photocopy, January 18, 1963 (Package 10)
    - Giant Sponge, poly bag, negative photocopy, May 17, 1962; 1 item (Package 10)
    - Bottle label, negative photocopy, 1 item (Package 10)
    - Miscellaneous poster material, 35 items (Package 10)
    - Miscellaneous sketches, 19 items (Package 10)
    - Products, sketches, January 21, 1964; 2 items (Package 10)
    - Products, sketches, January 6, 1964; 44 items (Package 10)
    - Products, sketches, 36 items (Package 10)
    - Liquid bicycle polish, June 1, 1968; 1 item (Package 10)
    - Titan Wax, poster display, June 8, 1962; 1 item (Package 10)
    - Vista Wax, poster display, 1 item (Package 10)
- Design Projects
  - A and A Plastics (Package 1)
  - Allied Farm Equipment, 2 envelopes (Package 1)
  - American Hospital Supply, 5 envelopes (Package 1)
  - A.I.D., 2 envelopes (Package 1)
  - A.M.R. (Package 1)
  - Brunswick Corp. (B.S.E.), 18 envelopes (Package 2)
  - Burgess Vibrocrafters Inc., 11 envelopes (Package 3)
  - Caudill, Rowlett, Scott (Package 3)
  - Continental Group (Package 3)
  - Cooper's Inc., 61 envelopes (Package 4)
  - Cooper's Inc., 1 envelope, 1 cardboard case (Package 5)
  - Corning Glass (Package 6)
  - Design Research Inc., 5 envelopes (Package 6)
  - E.F.S. (school), 2 envelopes (Package 6)
  - Eljer Co., 7 envelopes (Package 6)
  - Felt Products, 4 envelopes (Package 7)
  - Hankscraft Co., 12 envelopes (Package 7)
  - Hankscraft Co., 26 envelopes (Package 8)
  - Hankscraft Co., 18 envelopes (Package 9)
  - Hankscraft Co., 5 envelopes (Package 10)
  - Hamilton Beach, 10 envelopes (Package 11)
  - Hamilton Beach, 11 envelopes (Package 12)
  - Herman Nelson (Package 13)
  - Hudson's Bay, 7 envelopes (Package 13)
  - I.C.A. (Package 13)
  - I.D.S.A. (Package 13)
  - Illinois Testing Laboratories, 2 envelopes (Package 13)
  - Johnson Motors, 2 envelopes (Package 13)
  - Libby (Package 13)
  - Lilly (Package 13)
  - <ead Johnson and Co., 2 envelopes (Package 13)
  - Meadowbrook (Package 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 16 panels (Package 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 10 envelopes, 8 panels, sketches, 2 maps (Package 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1 panel (Package 16)
  - Miscellaneous sketches (Package 17)
  - Molson's Brewery Quebec Ltd, 4 envelopes (Package 18)
  - Owens-Corning (Package 18)
  - Panelfab Products, Inc (Package 18)
  - Puritron, 4 envelopes (Package 18)
  - Reeves, 4 envelopes (Package 18)